Ada Peirce McCormick papers, 1881-1978 (bulk 1920-1974)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: General Files, ca. 1915-1978
  - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA). 1941-1971 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - YWCA Convention. 1949 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - YWCA, National Chapter. 1942-1957 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - YWCA, The Women's Press. 19429-1949 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - YWCA, World Fellowship. 1944-1947 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Yuer, June Curtis (Leslie Van Eps). 1946-1957 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Zahn, Curtis. 1945-1947 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Zernov, Dr. Nicolas. 1941-1961 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Zinar, Ruth. 1952-1954 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Zinberg, Len. 1946-1949 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Zolotow, Maurice. 1943-1946 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Series III: Cabot Files, 1899-1975
  Contains correspondence, most of it between APM and her godparents, Richard C. (RCC) and Ella Lyman Cabot (ELC). Their long relationship produced a large volume of correspondence, with much of the content providing keen insight into APM's attitudes and opinions on life, marriage, and spiritual issues. After the death of ELC in 1934, RCC recruited APM to write the Cabot's biography, a task she never finished, although the Radcliffe Quarterly published APM's essay on ELC the following year. Her letters, drafts, and other material related to the project are contained within. Apart from the missives between APM and the Cabots is her correspondence with Alice O'Gorman, long-time secretary to RCC, Faith Cabot Pigors, RCC's niece, and her daughter, Phillipa Weld. Some of these letters regard the research and writing of the Cabot biography. Researchers should note that the letters from ELC and RCC to APM were copied and the originals sent to the Cabot Collection at Harvard University.
  - Allport, Gordon, Trustee, Ella Lyman Cabot Trust. 1958-1967 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Cabot Biography, drafts. 1936-1958 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Cabot Biography, drafts. No Date (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Cabot Biography, index. No Date (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Cabot Biography, purpose. 1952 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Cabot Papers (sent to Harvard). 1964-1975 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Cabot Seminar. 1957-1958 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Contract. 1936-1939 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Alice O' Gorman to APM. 1935-1964 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, APM to Alice O'Gorman. 1935-1936, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, APM and Faith Cabot Pigors. 1935-1938 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, APM and Faith Cabot Pigors. 1939-1946 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, APM and Faith Cabot Pigors. 1954-1961 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, APM and Phillipa Weld. 1939-1957 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, APM and Phillipa Weld. 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, APM Phillipa Weld. 1960-1963 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, APM and RCC. 1935 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, APM and RCC. 1936 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, APM to Alice O'Gorman. 1939-1954 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, APM to Alice O'Gorman. 1955 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, APM to Alice O'Gorman. 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, APM to Alice O'Gorman. 1958 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, APM to Alice O'Gorman. 1959 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, APM to Alice O'Gorman. 1960-1963 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, APM to Alice O'Gorman, re: Cabots. 1927-1958 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, APM to ELC. 1913-1920 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, APM to ELC. 1921-1922 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, APM to ELC. 1923-1927 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, APM to ELC. 1928-1932 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, APM to ELC. No Date (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, APM to ELC and RCC. 1922-1931 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, APM to ELC and RCC. No Date (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, APM to Hugh Cabot. 1943 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, APM to Ida M. Tarbell, "Virgil by Richard's Body." 1939 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC. 1912-1915 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC. 1916-1919 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC. 1920-1923 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC. 1924-1925 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC. 1926-1933 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC. 1934-1935 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC. 1936 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC. 1937-1939 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC and others re: finances of Cabot biography. 1935-1936, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, APM to RCC on marital relations. 1924, 1935 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, ELC to APM. 1913-1929 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, ELC to APM. ca. 1914-1934 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, MacMillan Company. 1938-1939 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, RCC to APM. 1912-1922 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, RCC to APM. 1914-1935 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, RCC to APM. 1936-1939 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, RCC to APM re: book. 1935-1939 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence regarding the ELC biography. 1935-1936 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Edward Twestleton Cabot. 1899 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - "Ella Lyman Cabot," APM thesis. 1936 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Ella Lyman Cabot Cup. ca. 1940 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - "Ella Lyman Cabot," Radcliffe Quarterly. 1935 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Ella Lyman Cabot Trust. 1954-1964 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Legal Agreement: Alice O'Gorman correspondence. 1957-1963 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Cabot material. 1935-1955 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - O'Gorman, Joseph. 1948-1972 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Richard Cabot Award. 1961-1966 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Starkey, Marian (collaborator on biography). 1955-1958 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Telephone conversations, APM to Alice O'Gorman. 1958 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Tarbell Files, 1891-1968
  Comprises correspondence, notes, reminiscences, and newspaper clippings. The bulk of material pertains to APM's friendship with mentor, Ida M. Tarbell (IMT). A journalist and biographer by profession, Tarbell served as consulting editor to Letter Magazine until her death in 1944. Most of the correspondence is between APM and IMT; however, there are several folders containing correspondence to and from IMT's relatives, and the McCormicks and Viola Roseboro, a manuscript reader for McClure's magazine and personal friend of IMT. Some originals were copied and sent to the Ida M. Tarbell Collection at Allegheny College (Pa). APM transcribed IMT letters to her family during the years 1891-1894 and these are found in a notebook. Drafts of APM's unpublished biography of IMT can be found in the Manuscripts series.
  - Boyden, Bert. No Date (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Checks sent to IMT. 1935-1944 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Checks sent to members of Tarbell family. 1940-1941 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and reminiscences, APM and Viola Roseboro re: IMT. 1929-1948 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and reminiscences, APM and Viola Roseboro. 1909-1944 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, APM and Clara Tarbell Tupper. 1931-1944 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, APM and Ella Tarberll. 1931-1968 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, APM and Esther Aldrich. 1941-1944 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, APM and Franklin Tarbell. 1938-1940 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, APM and Franklin Tarbell. 1941-1945 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, APM and Jane and Peter Lyon re: IMT biography. 1957, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, APM and John S. Phillips. 1943-1945 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, APM and John Trainer (lawyer for IMT estate). 1944-1948 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, APM and Linda Cornell. 1965 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, APM and Milton Rose (APM's lawyer) re: IMT estate. 1944-1952 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, APM and Mrs. John Finley. 1943-1944 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, APM and Mrs. W. W. Tarbell. 1930-1945 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, APM and Ray Stannard Baker. 1944 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, APM to Dorothy Canfield. 1944-1945 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, APM to Elizabeth Scott. 1944-1948 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, APM to Ella Tarbell. 1931, 1937 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, APM to Ella Tarbell. 1938 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT. 1923-1928 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT. 1929-1930 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT. 1931-1933 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT. 1935-1939 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT. 1940-1941 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT. 1942-1943 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT. No Date (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT re: Ella and Franklin Tarbell. 1936-1939 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, APM to IMT, "Vigil by Richard's Body." 1939 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, APM to others re: IMT. 1928-1946 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, APM to Sarah Tarbell. 1932-1950 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, APM to various people re: IMT estate. 1944 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, APM to Viola Roseboro. 1928 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, APM to Viola Roseboro. 1929 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, APM to Viola Roseboro. 1930 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, APM to Viola Roseboro. 1935-1945 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Ella Tarbell to APM. 1936-1937 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Ella Tarbell to APM. 1938-1939 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, FCM and Viola Roseboro. 1931-1933 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, IMT and Clara Tarbell Tupper. 1936-1944 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, IMT and Ray Stannard Baker. 1919-1943 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. 1923-1928 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. 1929 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. 1930 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. 1931-1933 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. 1934-1937 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. 1938-1939 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. 1940-1943 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. 1942-1943 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, IMT to APM. No Date (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, IMT to Sarah Tarbell. ca. 1925-1939 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Mollie Best to IMT. No Date (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence re: APM's claim against IMT estate. 1944-1945 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence re: IMT. 1940, 1944 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Drawings of IMT by APM. No Date (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Impressions of John D. Rockefeller by IMT. No Date (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - IMT and Jane Addams. 1931 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - IMT comments on Letter articles. 1942-1943 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - IMT, death and funeral. 1944 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - IMT lectures on biography (notes by APM). 1930 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - IMT lectures on biography (notes by APM). 1931 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - IMT on Cabots. 1936 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - IMT will. No Date (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - "Madame," by IMT. 1941-1942 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - News clippings. 1905-1944 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Notes, comments, and reminiscences about IMT. 1928-1930 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Notes, comments, and reminiscences about IMT. 1931 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Notes, comments, and reminiscences about IMT. 1936-1944 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Phillips, John S., re: "Ada and Ida." 1944 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Reminiscence of lunch with IMT and Viola Roseboro. 1935 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - IMT letters to her family (transcribed copies). 1891-1894 (Box 88, Folder 7-8)
- Series V: Manuscripts, 1906-1950
  A prolific writer whose interests knew few bounds, APM composed many essays and short stories, a number of which appeared in print. Her short story, "Richard," a biographical sketch on Theodore Roosevelt's grandson, appeared in a 1924 issue of Harpers. APM occasionally wrote under the pen name Charity Howard. Includes related correspondence.
  - APM manuscript record. 1923-1945 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - "Blackwater Blues," purchased by APM. No Date (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Book reviews by APM. 1926 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - "Character Calendar." 1923-1926 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - "Clothers and the Cook," by Charity Howard. ca. 1920s (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - "Discovering Grandmother," by Charity Howard. ca. 1920s (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - "Ella Lyman Cabot." 1935 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - "Exit the Cook." 1928-1931 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - "Exit the Cook," photographs and sketches. ca. 1926 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - "Family Relations." 1926 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - "George Du Maurier," graduation essay. 1906 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - "The Idle Apprentice." 1925 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - "If With All Your Hearts." 1950 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - "Novels to Put Over Ideas." 1926 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - "Richard." 1922-1931 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - "Richard." 1924, 1952 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - "Richard," correspondence. 1924-1931 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - "Richard," news clippings. 1924 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - "Sarah Brewster Lincoln." 1931 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - "The Scandalous Funeral of Mrs. Patterson." 1924-1927 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - "Schweitzer vs. Kinsey." 1948-1949 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - "The Terrors of Being Engaged." 1926-1929 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - "To a Wounded Man." 1945 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - "Wanted: A Place to Pray," by Charity Howard. 1923 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - "Write the Thing that Interests You." 1924 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Writers' Workshop, Mathilde Weil. 1923-1924 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - APM manuscript on Ida M. Tarbell. 1929-1948 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - APM manuscripts, correspondence. 1924-1942 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - APM plots and articles for class. 1931-1932 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - APM writings, miscellaneous. ca. 1924-1944 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - "Billy Sunday," autograph, drawings and photographs. 1925 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - "Billy Sunday," correspondence. 1930 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - "Billy Sunday," final draft. ca. 1925 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - "The Darkest Thing." No Date (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - "Dignity (Madame Kaytor)." No Date (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - "The Dumb Bell." 1924-ca. 1931 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - "The Expiation." ca. 1912 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - "Husbands and Wives," (used for marriage courses). ca. 1920s (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - "Maggie's Husband." 1924 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - "Mrs. Duncan's (Dollop's) Twins." 1931-1932 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - "The Pride of Dunstan Hall." 1931 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Reynolds, Paul (agent for APM). 1925-1932 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - "Sally in the Stock Market." 1933 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - "Socially Pushing our Daughters." 1925 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - "These Terrible Modern Books." ca. 1925 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - "We Have a Guest." No Date (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - "The Wicked Modern Novel." 1926 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Series VI: APM Articles and Research, 1926-1962
  Contains the musings of APM on a wide variety of issues, some in the form of correspondence to friends and colleagues. Most are written in a publishable format, although it is unclear if any of the pieces were submitted for publication or appeared in print. Included are the Arthur Herzog and Kinsey Report materials. APM hired Herzog, a former student at the University of Arizona, to do research on assorted topics. The content of the files reflect his findings. APM objected to the conclusions of the Kinsey Report regarding human sexuality and wrote several responses.
  - Advertising. 1945-1961 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Advice to New Widow on Employment. 1937 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Art, support of. 1950 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Art Promotion in Restaurants. 1963 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Authors. 1951 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Automobiles, Lack of Choice in. No Date (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Bicycling. 1961 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Books are Strangers. 1952 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Book Reviews. 1938-1952 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Book Review and Notes on many books. 1944-1955 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Censorship, Press, Freedom. 1950-1957 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Children and Orphans. 1942-1961 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Communism. 1951-1956 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Courage. 1926-1947 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Creative Work. 1954 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Crime. 1957 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Crime and Television. 1957-1961 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Foundations. 1952 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Freedom and Slavery. 1955 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Gandhi, Nehru and India. 1942-1958 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Herzog, Arthur, and APM correspondence. 1954-1961 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Herzog, Arthur, Articles. 1958 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Herzog, Arthur, Research. 1954-1956 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Herzog, Arthur, Research. 1956 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Herzog, Arthur, Research. January-June 1957 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Herzog, Arthur, Research. July-December 1957 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Herzog, Arthur, Research. 1958 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Human Relations and International Friendships. 1955 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Hurricane Names--Why Women? 1956 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Indian and Nehru. 1951 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Insurance, Life. 1937-1951 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Kinsey Galley Proofs (Never Published). 1950 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Kinsey Report, American College of Physicians. 1948 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Kinsey Report, APM and Kinsey correspondence. 1948-1954 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Kinsey Report, Articles by APM. 1949-1953 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Kinsey Report, Bonding of Sex Historians. 1953 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Kinsey Report, Institute for Sex Research, inc. 1953-1954 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Kinsey Report, Letter to Subscribers. 1949 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Kinsey Report, Miscellaneous Material. 1948-1950 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Kinsey Report, Rockefeller Interview by APM. 1949-1954 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Kinsey Report, "The Conditioning of a Sex Authority." No Date (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Leopold and Loeb Case. 1948-1953 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Love and Secrecy of the Mind. No Date (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Loyalty Oath. 1961 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Magazines. ca. 1948 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Marriage. 1926 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - McCarthy, Joe, Research. 1954 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Men of Genius. 1958 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Menninger, Karl, and Kinsey. 1953 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous. 1948-1957 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Movies and Censorship. 1937-1952 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Negroes. 1954 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Nervous and Mental Burdens. 1936-1950 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Schweitzer, Albert. 1946-1962 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Scientists' Responsibility. 1958 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Suicides and Nervous Burdens. 1942-1961 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Taxation. 1950-1957 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Television Research. 1957-1961 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Television Research, by Dick Olson for APM. 1961-1962 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Tennis. 1952 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Union Now, Pros and Cons. 1942 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - World War II. 1942-1957 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Series VII: Business Activities, 1939-1968
  Contains correspondence, policy statements, advertisements, awards, dividends, drawings and additional material related to the operation of Letter magazine and other business ventures of APM.
  - Account Ledgers, 1942-1951
    - Ledger. 1942-1946 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Ledger. 1947-1948 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Ledger. 1949-1951 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Advertising, 1942-1954
    - Advertising. 1945-1954 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Advertising Ideas. 1942-1946 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Advertising, Magazines and Newspapers. 1944-1947 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Advertising, Magazines and Newspapers. 1948-1953 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Advertising, Telephone Directories. 1945-1953 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Advertising, The Writer. 1943-1950 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Listing of Letter in directories and periodicals. 1949-1953 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Soliciting advertisements. 1942-1943 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Tallantyre, Renee, Publicity work for Letter. 1945 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Awards, 1941-1968
    - Advertising Award. 1947 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Award ribbons. No Date (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Awards. 1943-1968 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Awards, arranged by field. 1941-1953 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Awards, certificates. 1948-1953 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Corporations Considered by APM, 1942-1968
    - Character-Intelligence Book Club. 1951-1952 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Character-Intelligence Book Club correspondence. 1951-1952 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Character-Intelligence Research. 1947-1954 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Consultant on Civilian Morale. 1942, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Research Recognitions, articles of incorporation. 1968 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Dividends, 1944-1952
    - Dividend covers. 1944-1951 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Dividends, miscellaneous. 1945-1950 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Record of Dividends. 1944-1952 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Drawings in Letter Magazine, 1943-ca. 1947
    - Division headings. No Date (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 1, no. 1). 1943 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 1, no. 2). 1943 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 1, no. 3). 1943 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 1, no. 4). 1944 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 2, no. 5). 1944 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 2, no. 6). 1945 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 3, no. 7). 1945 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 4, no. 8). 1946 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Drawings and half-tones (v. 5, no. 9). 1947 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Drawings by others for Letter. No Date (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Drawings, originals by Jane Kiersch. No Date (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Pictures of cuts to be used in issue no. 10. No Date (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Exhibits, 1945-1956
    - Arizona State Fair. 1947-1948 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Letter activities. 1945-1956 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Record of Letter book exhibits. 1946-1953 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Religious books. 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - History and Policy of Letter Magazine, 1942-1950
    - Classification of material in Letter. 1943-1947 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - History and policy of Letter. 1942-1950 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Policy and purpose of Letter. 1942-1950 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Editor, 1942-1952
    - Acknowledgements for gifts of dividends. 1944 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Acknowledgements for gifts of dividends. 1945 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Acknowledgements for gifts of dividends. 1946 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Acknowledgements for gifts of dividends. 1947-1948 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Acknowledgements for gifts of dividends. 1950-1952 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Acknowledgements, miscellaneous. 1943-1950 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Index to Letter Magazine, 1941-1947
    - Notebook, complete index to Letter. No Date (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Subseries XI: Letter Magazine (complete run), 1943-1947
    - Letter. 1943-1947 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Author's page, information about authors. 1945-1947 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Congratulatory letters. 1942-1943 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Letters to the Editor. 1943-1944 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Letters to the Editor. 1945 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Letters to the Editor. 1946 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Letters to the Editor. 1947 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Letters to the Editor. 1948 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Letters to the Editor. 1949-1950, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Permission to Print. 1943-1947 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Mexican Contest, 1944-1945
    - Mexican contest, articles published in Letter. 1944-1945 (Box 98, Folder 10)